Launching lib\main.dart on Chrome in debug mode...
Waiting for connection from debug service on Chrome...             68.7s

Flutter run key commands.
r Hot reload. 
R Hot restart.
h List all available interactive commands.
d Detach (terminate "flutter run" but leave application running).
c Clear the screen
q Quit (terminate the application on the device).

This app is linked to the debug service: ws://127.0.0.1:50663/Zd8GMB-6Av0=/ws
Debug service listening on ws://127.0.0.1:50663/Zd8GMB-6Av0=/ws
A Dart VM Service on Chrome is available at: http://127.0.0.1:50663/Zd8GMB-6Av0=
The Flutter DevTools debugger and profiler on Chrome is available at: http://127.0.0.1:50663/Zd8GMB-6Av0=/devtools/?uri=ws://127.0.0.1:50663/Zd8GMB-6Av0=/ws
Starting application from main method in: org-dartlang-app:///web_entrypoint.dart.
